<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>Todo list</title>
        <author email="c95men at users.sourceforge.net">Markus Eriksson</author>
    </properties>
    <body>
        <section name="Introduction">
            <p>
				This is a short TODO list with things that should be fixed in smsj. Please let me know if you
				would like to help out with anything on this list, or if you have something that should be 
				added to this list.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Update the 7bit charset encoder/decoder">
            <p>
                The current 7bit charset encoder/decoder is incomplete. There are some characters that must be
                encoded as two 7bit characters.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Remove GsmOperators class">
            <p>
                Is this class really neccessary? It is not a complete listing anyway...
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Create a demo app">
            <p>
                There should be a simple demo app. Either a command line tool or a swing application.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Complete the EMS support">
            <p>
                The current EMS implementation is only a stub implementation. I created a bunch of classes
                but never completed the implementation.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Update the UCP transport">
            <p>
                The current UCP transport is currently in a bad shape. It should work to submit simple
                text messages, but I'm unsure if UDH, 8bit and UCS2 messages works. I would really like
                to have some help here since I don't have access to an UCP server right now.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Complete the MMS part">
            <p>
                The MMS part is perhaps 75% done. The API is a bit rough as well.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Add query, cancel and replace to the sms transport API">
            <p>
                Should be quite simple to add.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Add an asynchronous transport API">
            <p>
                This would really be a boost for smsj. This would make it possible to use smsj in
                implementations that need to send alot of SMS but at the same time keep track
                of all messages.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Add support for incoming SMS">
            <p>
                This feature is perhaps the most requested feature.
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Add OMA DRM encoder.">
            <p>
                Add a new MimeMultipart type that can wrap OMA drm files. 
			</p>
        </section>
        <section name="Add tutorial and documentation.">
            <p>
                The documentation that is available today is a bit thin. 
			</p>
        </section>
    </body>
</document>
